export const flashcardSet = [{
  id: 1,
  question: "tung3 (痛)",
  answer: "Pain, sorrow, bitter"
}, {
  id: 2,
  question: "gung1 cing4 si1 (工程師)",
  answer: "Engineer"
}, {
  id: 3, 
  question: "syut3 (雪)",
  answer: "Snow"
}, {
  id: 4,
  question: "fo2 (火)",
  answer: "Fire"
}, {
  id: 5,
  question: "cing1 (清)",
  answer: "Clear, to clean"
}, {
  id: 6,
  question: "lou5 (路)",
  answer: "Road, path"
}, {
  id: 7,
  question: "siu2 (笑)",
  answer: "To laugh, smile"
}, {
  id: 8,
  question: "mung6 (夢)",
  answer: "Dream"
}, {
  id: 9,
  question: "pui3 (陪)",
  answer: "To accompany"
}, {
  id: 10,
  question: "soeng2 (想)",
  answer: "To think, to want, to wish"
}];